自人类文明伊始，娃娃便深受孩子喜爱
为收藏者所珍视，以及在宗教仪式中作为连接善恶的渠道
光是想就让我们害怕
It scares us just thinking about it.
你听了之后肯定会觉得我们疯了
When you hear it you're gonna think we're insane.
刚开始都是小事
It started out small,
像是一只手或是一条腿 变了方向
Like a leg or a hand was in a different position and...
然后是它的头朝上看 而不是向下
And it's head was looking up instead of down and...
接着有一天 就是出现在完全不同的房间
Then one day it was in a completely different room.
是它自己动的
It's moving around by itself.
卡米拉找了灵媒
Camilla got in touch with a medium.
她说娃娃被一个叫安娜贝尔·希金斯的女孩附身了
We learned from her that the doll was possessed by a girl named Annabelle Higgins.
她失去了双亲 喜欢上了我的娃娃
She had lost her parents and had taken a liking to my doll.
她只是想做朋友
All she wanted was to be friends.
我们听了之后 觉得很同情她
When we heard this we felt really sorry for her I mean...
我们是护士 就是帮助他人的
We're nurses We help people.
可之后…情况就变坏了
But then... Things got worse.
你是怎么得到它的？
How did you end up with it?
是妈妈送我的生日礼物
It was a gift from my mom for my birthday.
我不知道她是哪里来的
I don't know where she got it.
但是…我们害怕极了
But... We are beyond terrified.
《安娜贝尔》
(圣莫尼卡 加州  一年前)
上帝重视牺牲
God honour sacrifice.
我们的牺牲会打动上帝的心
And our sacrifices touch god's heart.
感动他的手
And move his hand.
耶稣说 这是我的命令
Jesus said: This is my commandment.
像我爱你般爱彼此
That you love one another as I have loved you.
没有比这更伟大的爱
Greater love hath no-one than this.
为朋友舍命
That he lay down his life for his friends.
让我们来祷告
Let us pray.
我也很高兴见到你 回头见
Good to see you too See you soon.
嘿 你好
Hey you!
好 那…谁赢了？
Ok So eh... Who won?
约翰 不过他作弊
John But he cheats.
什么？我…是以一敌二啊
What? I Ehh. It was two against one.
不得不采取措施 对吧？
I had to do something right?
是啊 没错
Yeah Right!
- 莎朗去哪儿了？ - 我们去找她
- Where did Sharon get off to? - We'll find her.
谢谢 拜
Thanks Bye.
皮特让你来找我的？
Pete send you after me?
我敢说 有天他会以为我也…
I swear one day he thinks I'll just...
一跑了之
run off too.
男人啊
Men!
没了我们 他们可怎么活？说真的
What would they be without us? I mean honestly.
- 最后的演讲很精彩 - 没什么
- We appreciate the last speech. - Sure thing.
你务必代我们照顾好这位太太和宝宝
You just make sure to take care of this wife and baby for us.
我们有问过名字了吗？
Did we ask about names yet?
- 莎朗 - 怎么了？
- Sharon! - What?!
我不是八卦 就是聊聊天
It's not prying It's just conversation.
我们还在琢磨呢
We're still working on them anyway.
不过我们基本肯定 约翰 如果是男孩的话
But we're pretty sure... John if it's a boy.
女孩就叫菲丽丝
And we're thinking Phyllis if it's a girl.
- 是吗？ - 是啊 你说你喜欢的
- We were? - Yeah You said you liked it.
- 我可没说过 - 是我祖母的名字
- He I never said that. - It's my grandmother's name.
- 我受不了你祖母 - 哎哟
- And I can't stand your grandmother. - Oh dear.
不只是我 根本没人受得了她
It's not only me I mean nobody can stand her.
是啊 她说得没错 大家都讨厌她
No she's right Everyone hates her.
好了 说到这里
Ok Well... On that note Sharon.
咱们进去吧 这两位需要好好谈一下
Let's go inside These two they have a lot to talk about.
- 谢谢 - 没什么的
- Thank you and... - Think nothing of it.
记住…孩子是恩赐
Just remember... children are a blessing.
确实是 然后他们学会了讲话
Indeed they are. And then they learn to talk.
看来你不同意叫"菲丽丝"？
I guess that's a no on Phyllis?
我们不该当着他们的面聊太多宝宝的事
We shouldn't talk about the baby so much in front of them.
- 那样不好 - 为什么
- It just aint right. - Why not?
他们两年前才失去了女儿
Well they only lost their daughter two years ago.
失去了女儿？米娅？
Lose their daughter? Mia?
她是离家出走 加入了嬉皮士
She ran away and joined up with the hippies.
现在估计已经有三个老公 改名叫"星星"了
By now she's probably got three husbands and calls herself Star.
就是叫"星星"
Well... "Even Star"
也比菲丽丝好听
is a better name than Phyllis.
你…你没锁门？
You... you didn't lock it?
没啊 干嘛要锁？
No Why would I?
你得开始记得锁门了 约翰 现在…
You have to start locking it John I mean it's...
现在不一样了
it's a different world now.
他们自称为"家族"
They call themselves "The Family".
但警方将其定性为危险的邪教
But police officials have labelled them a dangerous cult
居住在施潘牧场内
residing on the grounds of Spahn Ranch.
那里曾作为很多著名西部片的背景
Once used as the backdrop for many well-known westerns.
"家族" 估计有将近三十名成员
The Family is estimated to have close to thirty gatherers
其中很多都有大量药物史和犯罪行为
Many of them with histories of heavy drug use and criminal behaviour.
目前正被拘留 等待
Are in custody awaiting charges...
残忍杀害泰特和拉比安卡一案的起诉
for the brutal Tate and LaBianca murders.
他们使得洛杉矶人心惶惶
They held Los Angeles in the grip of fear...
在警探掌握嫌犯线索之前…
before police investigators were led to the suspects...
亲爱的 能关掉电视吗
Hey Honey?! Do you think you could shut off the TV?
搞得我有点难以集中精神
It's making it a little hard to concentrate.
他们的领导者 查理斯·曼森
Their leader Charles Manson was sometimes referred to
被他的追随者视为上帝和撒旦的化身
as both God and Satan by his devoted followers...
并预言有"世界末日"般的事件发生 称之为"混乱游戏"
had predicted an Armageddon like event he called Helter Skelter
多谢
Thank you!
嘿 听我说 你不该看这种东西
Hey, u know. You shouldn't even be watching that stuff.
好吗 可能会令宝宝不安的 有新的研究显示…
Alright It could upset the baby. There's new research out there...
- 哎哟 又有新研究啊 - 是真的
- Oh boy! More new research? - It's true!
他们发现宝宝在子宫内
They are learning that the babies in utero
对外面世界的感知 要超出人们的想象
experience more of the outside world than they ever thought possible.
他们懂得识别声音和噪音 歌曲
They recognize voices and noises Songs.
我肯定研究这个的人花了好几百万
You know, I bet the man that did that research spent millions of dollars
明明只要免费问自己老妈就可以了
when they could have just asked the mother for free.
- 你这边怎么样？ - 嗯…
- How's it going in here? - Well...
我在尽全力投入进去
I am trying my hardest to enjoy it.
每个人都在跟我说
Everyone keeps telling me that...
只要开始实习 事情就会更加难搞
Once you're in the residency it gets a million times worse.
还没提过我是个准爸爸
Haven't even mentioned the fact that I'm about to be a new father.
- 为什么？ - 不知道
- Why not? - I don't know.
有时就是不想听人说…
Sometimes you just don't wanna hear how difficult...
- 会有多难 - 难？
- It's gonna be. - Difficult?
你知道的 或许说"难"不对
You know Maybe difficult's not the right word.
挑战
Challenging.
你是说实习
Are you talking about the residency
还是我和宝宝啊
or me and the baby.
不知道
I don't know.
我想是全部吧 我是说…
All of it I guess I mean...
眼下对我来说并不是个理想的状态
It's not like this is an ideal situation for what I'm about to go through.
我…我们…对我们来说
I. We. We're about to go through.
我并不是那个意思的 抱歉
I didn't mean for that to sound like it did I'm sorry.
不是说…
It's not like...
困难 挑战 或是什么坏事儿的
difficult or challenging or bad things anyway.
听着…
Look..
我知道我有点…
I know that I've been a little...
只顾忙自己的事 有人或许会说太自我中心
caught up in my own world lately Some people might call it self centered.
- 有人？ - 大多数人
- Some people? - Most people.
每个人
Everyone.
我们能倒个带 过去两分钟重来一次吗？
Can we just go back and redo the last two minutes please?
求你了？
Please?
没事
It's fine.
我知道你有压力
I know you were stressed.
我就是最近
I'm just a little
有点太敏感了
over sensitive lately.
- 想要我告诉你原因吗？ - 是的 医生
- Do you want me to tell you why? - Yes Doctor!
用我…
In my...
几乎…专业的意见
almost... expert opinion
你有点敏感
You are a little sensitive
是因为你怀孕了
because you are a lot pregnant.
嘿 很抱歉 我…我是
Hey I'm sorry I mean... I am...
是的 医学院快毕业了 我压力有点大
Yes I'm. I'm stressed about finishing med-school
有点害怕竞争 但是…
and I'm freaking out about matching but...
我从没这么幸福过 从没
I've never been happier Ever.
好吗？那都是因为你
Ok? And that's because of you.
还有小家伙
And it.
知道吗
You know what?
有样东西我想给你
There's something I wanna give you.
别啊 上次你这么说 结果我被搞大肚子了
Oh no The last time you said that I ended up pregnant
没错 是的
Yes you did.
好了 闭上眼睛
Ok Close your eyes.
我本想等到宝宝出生 不过…
I was waiting on this until the baby but...
你觉得有点…
You were feeling a little...
内疚 是 因为是我说的
Guilty yes Because of what I said.
好了 睁开眼睛吧
Ok Open your eyes.
你不是吧…
You didn't...
- 天啊 约翰 - 就是这个 对吗？
- My god John. - That's the one right?
是的
Yes.
你在哪儿找到她的？我是说…
Where did you find her? I mean...
- 你知道我找了多久吗？ - 我知道
- Do you know how long I've been looking? - I know.
我都彻底放弃了
I had completely lost hope.
我有我的办法
Oh I have my ways.
未来几个月房租可能会比较紧张 不过…
We'll be a little short on the rent the next few of months but eh...
瞧 刚刚好
There She fits right in.
- 这样一组就全了 是吧 - 是的
- That completes the set-up right? - Yes It does.
谢谢 我爱她
Thank you I love her.
约翰？约翰 醒醒
John? John Wake up.
怎么了？是宝宝吗？
What is it? The baby?
不 不是 隔壁 我听到尖叫声
No no Next door. I heard a scream.
我…我觉得有点不对劲
I... I think something's wrong.
待在这儿 我去看看
Stay here I'm gonna check it out.
约翰 等下 我们不应该报警吗？
John Wait Shouldn't we call the cops?
因为你觉得听到了尖叫？
Because you think you heard a scream?
先让我看看 换他们也会这么做的
Just let me go check it out They'd do the same for us.
他们要是听到我叫 我宁愿他们立刻报警
If they heard me scream I'd rather they call the cops.
是"认为"听到了你尖叫
Think they heard you scream.
- 当心 - 我会的
- Just be careful. - I will.
约翰？
John?
天啊 你浑身是血
Oh my god! You're covered in blood.
不是我的 快进去 马上叫救护车
It's not mine Go back inside and call an ambulance right now.
快去
Go...
- 911接线员 - 我…我需要救护车
- 911 operator. - I need. I need an ambulance.
地址是？
What's your location?
园丁路307号
307 Gardener Road.
- 对 - 是什么紧急情况？
- Yes. - What's your emergency?
我…我不知道 但是…
I. I don't know But..
有很多血
There's a lot of blood.
请尽快赶过来
Please Just be as fast as possible.
我喜欢你的娃娃们
I like your dolls.
我…我丈夫马上就回来了
My. My husband's coming back.
你…
Just... Just...
你想要什么就拿 赶紧走吧
Take whatever you want Just. Just get out.
出去 快离开这里 米娅
Get out Get out of here.
开门
Open up!
开门 是警察 把门打开
Open up! It's the police! Open the door!
你没事 有我们在
You're alright We got you.
我在这儿 我就在你身边呢
I'm right here I'm right here with you.
据一名警探描述 这悲惨的一幕
In a tragic scene described by one investigator
令人联想到可怕的邪教仪式
as reminiscent of a horrific cult ritual.
一对夫妻被残忍地捅死
A man and his wife was brutally stabbed to death
凶手便是他们离家出走的女儿安娜贝尔·希金斯
by their estranged daughter Annabelle Higgins.
以及不明身份的男友
And her unidentified boyfriend.
警方认为这两人是邪教成员
The two are believed to be members of a cult.
警方到达现场时 男性嫌犯已经中枪死亡
The male suspect was shot and killed as police arrived on scene.
其女儿则看似是死于自杀
While the daughter was found in an apparent suicide
喉咙被划开
her throat slit open.
一名警员对如此血腥谋杀的总结就是
One officer summed up these blood soaked murders by saying:
工作多年 我从未见过如此可怕的景象
In all my years I have never seen anything quite as gruesome as this.
羊膜肯定没有被刺穿
Damn well the amniotic sac wasn't punctured.
也没有破裂
And isn't ruptured.
有受到压迫的迹象
We are seeing signs of strain
在颈部
on the cervix.
多半是由于外部创伤造成
Most likely caused by the trauma.
所以呢
Which is why...
我要让你孕期剩下的日子里都卧床休息
I am putting you on bed rest for the remainder of your pregnancy.
现在…
Now...
你可以起来去方便了
You can get up and use the facilities.
如果你很敏感的话
If you do so delicately.
但除此之外的任何事 都会让你和你的孩子有危险
But anything beyond that would be putting you and your child at risk.
好吗？
Alright?
- 谢谢 - 好的
- Thank you! - Ok.
锁门
The lock!
我让他们把每样东西都洗刷了 起码两遍
I had them scrub everything At least twice.
都可以在里面做手术 很干净的
You can perform surgery in there It's so clean.
你不用这么做的
You didn't have to do that.
要是不这样 卧床久了你会发疯的
You're on bed rest for a while You'd go crazy if I didn't.
不要沉迷于日间肥皂剧就好了
Just Don't get all obsessed with those daytime soaps.
你知道我根本不喜欢的
You know I can't stand them.
回头我再把你的针线活拿来
I'll bring your sewing back in later on.
好吗？我们可以把整间房变成你的血汗工厂
Ok? We can turn the whole room into your own little sweatshop.
怎么了？
What is it?
你说孩子不会有事吧？
You think the baby is Ok?
宝宝都不知道发生了什么
The baby is not even aware of what happened.
真的吗？因为我听说有个新的研究…
Oh really? Because I heard there's some new research that...
是啊
Oh yeah.
你也听到医生说的了 只要你听话 宝宝就不会有事
You heard the doctors. So if you listen to them the baby is fine.
宝宝没事的
The baby is fine.
你是孩子他妈 对吗？不好的话你肯定知道的
You're its mother right? If it wasn't you would know.
- 如果真的出事呢？ - 什么？
- What if something does happen? - What?
- 会发生什么？ - 比如 我要生产的时候 约翰
- What's gonna happen? - When... Like when I go into labor John.
是啊
Yeah.
你会选择保孩子吗
You'll save the baby over me?
- 别这样 - 我们得谈一下这个
- Come on. - We have to talk about it.
我无法接受宝宝有任何闪失
I mean I can't have it If anything ever happened to it.
嘿 答应我
Hey promise me.
答应我你会保孩子的
You promise me you'll save the baby.
好 好 我答应你
Yeah Yeah I promise.
不过你知道吗？不会有事的
But you know what? It's gonna be okay.
你们都会好好的
You are gonna be fine
什么声音？
What the hell is that?
约翰
John!
约翰？
John?
没事
It's okay.
我是你朋友 你知道的 对吗？
I'm your friend. You know that don't you?
- 你是菲尔？ - 当然了
- Are you Phil? - Of course I am.
那我有朋友了
Well then I have a friend.
你一直…
You have been...
晚饭后…
After dinner...
甚至是跳舞
even dancing.
- 今天怎么样？ - 电视又坏了
- How'd it go today? - TV went out again.
是吗？
Really?
肯定是房间的关系 在小屋从来没有过
Must be that room It never did that in the den.
都是什么东西啊
What is all that?
这是我在商店随便买的几样东西
This is a bunch of random stuff that I picked up at the store.
来给孕妇解馋的
To satisfy any pregnancy cravings.
有意思的是 我并没有想吃东西的感觉
That's funny I haven't really had any cravings.
泡菜
Pickles.
天啊 你知道什么最配泡菜吗？
My god you know what would go really well with Pickles?
约翰·戈登 我们是天生一对儿
John Gordon We are meant to be together.
是啊 我知道 就像芥末和泡菜
Yeah I know Like Mustard and Pickles.
- 你今天有个很重要的会议 是吧 - 是的
- Did you have that big meeting today? - Yeah I did.
他认为我很有希望留在亨廷顿纪念医院
He thinks I've got a real shot at Huntington memorial.
当然了
Of course you do.
不过是在帕萨迪纳
It's in Pasadena though.
离海边很远 可以吗？
So further from the beach Okay with that?
换换风景也挺好
Change of view would be good.
是啊
Yeah.
萨克拉门托有个一天的会议 他认为我应该参加
There's this one day conference in Sacramento that he thinks I should attend.
对我朝那个方向发展有帮助
That could help move things in that direction.
过几天要飞过去一天
Fly up for a day in a few days.
就一两天？
Only a couple of days?
我没问题的
I'll be fine.
你得上床休息了
We gotta get you back to bed.
不应该坐这么久的
You shouldn't be sitting up this long.
克拉金警探今天来电话了
And Detective Clarkin called today.
说他这星期抽空想过来一趟
Said he wanted to stop by at some point this week.
我都已经告诉他了
I've already told him everything.
我…更愿意忘记整件事
I... I'd rather just forget the whole thing.
我知道 他只是说想再问几件事
I know He just said he wanted to go over a few things.
那个娃娃
The doll.
我们得丢掉它 当时就抱在她手里
We need to get rid of it I mean she had it in her hands.
不 你是对的 你说得对
No You're right You're right.
你就…放心吧
Just Consider it gone.
我想你可以告诉克拉金警探 他方便的话随时可以
I suppose you can tell Detective Clarkin he can stop by whenever's convenient.
反正我一时半会儿哪也不会去
It's not like I'm going anywhere anytime soon.
他们是邪教成员
They were members of a cult.
我们确认了是希金斯的女儿
We've confirmed that it was Higgins daughter.
和她男朋友
And her boyfriend.
- 你可能看过新闻了 - 邪教在统治全世界
- You may have heard on the news. - That cults are taking over the world.
并没有他们所让你认为的那样普遍
It's not quite as prevalent as they'd have you believe.
恐怕你很难说服我们相信这一点
You're gonna have a hard time convincing us of that.
他们是信奉撒旦吗？
Were they satanic?
没事 她应该知道
It's okay She should know.
是的
Yes.
是的 没错 认为他们是对神秘学感兴趣
Yes it is It is believed they had interest in the occult.
这样做是为了证明他们的皈依
That they did this to prove their devotion.
算是一种 为了表现暴力的暴力
A sort of. Violence for violence's sake.
可是太疯狂了
But that's crazy.
疯子干疯事儿 女士
Crazy people do crazy things Ma'am.
不过仅此而已
But that's all this was.
听我说
I tell you what.
我会再深入调查 看能有什么结果
I'll dig a little deeper See what I can find.
但如果有进一步结果
But if I come up with anything further,
- 我会再… - 不
- I'll reach anoth... - No!
谢谢
Thank you.
不过 除非是关系到我们的安全 不然我…
But... Unless it has something to do with our safety I...
我不想再听到任何有关的消息
I'd rather not hear any more about it.
好 我明白
Okay I understand.
好 就这样 就这样
Okay! Hold it right right right there.
- 谢谢 - 我去做爆米花
- Thank you! - I'm making popcorn.
你确定宝宝可以吃这么多奶油 还有…
Are you sure it's okay for the baby to have this much butter and...
- 你感觉怎么样？ - 紧张
- How are you feeling? - Well nervous.
他们会爱上你的
They are gonna love you.
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you too.
我来了 别怕
I got you I got you.
很抱歉我没有在
I'm so sorry that I wasn't here.
- 我很抱歉 - 你身后
- I'm so sorry - Behind you.
祝贺
Congratulations.
- 是个女孩儿 - 这是我的孩子
- It's a girl. - This is my baby.
天啊
Oh my gosh.
丽娅？
Leah?
丽娅
Leah.
嗨 丽娅 我是你爸爸
Hi Leah It's your daddy.
瞧她啊 看看她
Look at her Look at her.
约翰
John.
约翰 火
John The fire.
没事 她很好 你也很好
It's fine. She's fine You're fine.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what happened.
感觉这房子被诅咒了
It's like the house is cursed.
我没办法再回到那里去了
I can never go back there again.
我做不到 现在有了她
I can't Not with her now.
你永远都不用再回去
You don't have to Ever.
(加州 帕萨迪纳)
- 嘿 亲爱的 准备好了吗？ - 现在随时…
- Hey honey, you all set? - Any second now...
她都会…
She's gonna...
然后…
And then...
你得出去走走 来吧
You need to get out more Come on.
- 我们要迟到了 - 我们真的要去吗？
- We'll be late! - You really think we should go?
丽娅有点迷糊
I mean Leah's being a little fuzzy.
米娅 她没事的
Mia She's fine.
好吗 你们俩都需要离开这里 关在这里待太久了
Ok You both need to get out of here You've been cooped up in here too much.
我知道 可是…
I know but it's...
快看 看啊 出去走走 外面多美 好吗
Look look Get outta here It's beautiful Okay?
拜托 你需要 我也需要 丽娅
Come on You need this I need this Leah...
她绝对需要多一些色彩的
She could definitely use some color.
行了你
Stop it.
弄点那什么…你怎么说的来着
Put some of that... What do you call it?
可可奶油牛奶
Cocoa Butter Milk.
我们给她涂点可可奶油
We should just slap her with some Cocoa Butter.
好啦好啦 我去 只要你别再念了
Okay okay! I will go as long as you stop talking.
保证
We promise.
- 我们走 - 走啦
- Let's go! - Come on.
不能让恐惧控制我们
We cannot let fear control us.
因为与上帝同行时 我们绝不孤单
For we are never truly alone when we walk with God.
是否对一样事物了解越多 我们的恐惧就越少？
Isn't it true that the more we know about something the less fear we have from it?
我们要面对恐惧
We need to face our fears
才能更了解恐惧
to better understand them.
我们要用一道亮光
We need to shine a bright light...
照射依赖于我们的
on the monsters that feed
不安 焦虑
on our insecurities on our anxieties.
以及自我怀疑而生存的怪物
And on the doubt that we cast on ourselves.
我们要记住 对那些有信念的人来说
We need to remember that for those who have faith
真理的人生是不朽的
this life of truth is everlasting.
米娅
Mia.
介意我给你的小家伙拍张照吗？
Mind if I take a picture of your little one?
我喜欢把会众中最新成员的照片
I like hang photos of the newest members of the congregation
贴在来访公告板上
on the visitors bulletin board.
好 当然可以
Ah yes Sure Of course.
不不不 把她抱在你腿上
No no no Hold her on your lap.
- 你不用连我一起拍的 - 当然需要
- Oh you don't need me in the photo. - Of course I do...
母亲比其他生灵更接近上帝
Mothers are closer to God than any other living creature.
只有她们可以分享上帝创造性的奇迹
For only they can share in God's creative miracle.
一 二 三
Uno dos tres.
好极了 应该可以了
Wonderful! That should do it.
每个礼拜日我都还能感受到希金斯夫妇的缺席
I still feel the Higgins' absence every Sunday.
- 我想肯定很… - 约翰在那儿 我该走了
- I imagine it must be dif. - There's... There's John I should go.
我们还有很多箱子要拆封
We still have a lot of boxes to unpack.
很遗憾 我…
Well unfortunately I...
我没有可以帮你的祷告式
I don't have a prayer to help you with that.
我…
Well I...
我想有些事是要靠自己的
guess there are some things we need to take care of ourselves.
是啊
Yes.
再会
Goodbye.
佩雷斯神父
Father Perez.
我想这是最后一箱了
I think this is the last of them.
准备开香槟了
Somebody pop the Champagne.
我去看她
I'll get her.
慢着 怎么会有那个的 我发誓我丢掉了的
Wait a sec How'd that get in there? I swear I threw it out.
我不知道
I don't know.
肯定是火灾之后弄混了
Things must have gotten mixed up after the fire.
来 给我吧
Here. Give her to me.
不 不用
No No.
这是你送我的礼物
You gave her to me as a gift.
佩雷斯神父说我们要相信我们的力量
Like Father Perez said we should celebrate our strength right?
你确定？
You sure?
是的
Yeah.
瞧 刚刚好
There She fits right in.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
抱歉 谢谢
Oh sorry Thank you.
你们也住在这儿吗？
Do you live here too?
- 我们住在… - 别告诉她
- We live in... - Don't tell her.
我们不能说
Were not supposed to tell.
她是陌生人
She's a stranger.
这是很好的规矩呢
That's a very good rule to have.
我喜欢你的娃娃 我也有一个
I like your doll I have one just like it.
你也有？
You too?
其实不只一个
A few actually.
我是米娅 她是丽娅
I'm Mia and this is Leah.
是啊 你叫什么名字？
Yeah What's your name?
- 是南… - 我说了别告诉她
- It's Nan... - I said don't tell her!
好吧
Well...
或许有天我们可以成为朋友
Maybe one day we can all be friends.
- 你是巴美拉的新住客 是不是 - 是的
- You're the new tenants at the Palmyra aren't you? - Yes.
我想这个小家伙看什么都很新鲜吧
I suppose this little one is pretty much new to everything?
这是丽娅
This is Leah.
她真可爱
She's adorable.
我…我是米娅
I. I'm Mia.
伊芙林 嗨
Evelyn. Hi.
来 这是我女儿最喜欢的
Here This is my daughters favorite.
或许等丽娅大一点 她也会喜欢的
Maybe Leah will like it too when she's a little older.
太有心了 谢谢
That's very sweet Thank you.
- 随时都欢迎你来 - 谢谢
- Well feel free to stop by any time. - Thank you.
看看他们给你画了什么
Look what they drew for you.
看到吗 是我们
See? That's us.
已经交到朋友了呢
Making friends already.
咱们锻炼锻炼身体
I guess we're getting a little exercise.
瞧这个
Look at this.
我们要…找他们父母谈谈吗？
Should we... Talk to their parents?
如果丽娅做出这种事 我…我会想知道的
If Leah did something like this I would wanna know about it.
丽娅肯定不会这样的
Leah would never do anything like this.
画得一点都不好 瞧瞧这比例
This isn't even good I mean. Look at the proportions.
约翰
John!
是的 米娅 如果她这样 我也想知道的
Yes Mia. If she did I would wanna know too.
好吗 所以我们走
Okay? So lets go...
看他们住在哪儿 自我介绍一下
Find out where they live Introduce ourselves.
但不要小题大做 好吗？
But let's not make a big deal outta this Okay?
这又不是威胁什么的
It's not like this is a threat or anything.
只是小孩子过分夸张的想象
It's just one kid with an overactive imagination.
我知道 我知道
I know I... I know I know.
你要记住 我们搬到这里是为了远离过去
You gotta remember that we moved here to get away from what happened.
我们收拾了衣服 打包了家具
We packed up our clothes We packed up our furniture.
还有美好的回忆 但是恐惧？
We packed up the good memories. But the fears?
和焦虑？我们说好统统留在过去的
And the anxieties? We promised to leave those behind.
不是说起来那么容易的 约翰
It is not as easy as it sounds John.
听着 我很抱歉 好吗 听我说
Look. I'm sorry... Okay You know what?
明晚
Tomorrow night.
我不用加班 好吗 所以…
I don't have to work late okay so...
我说我回家来 咱们坐下
I say I come home We sit down.
享受一顿美餐
We have a nice dinner.
我们来一个…成年人之间的对话
And we have some... Adult conversation.
好吗？
Okay?
可以吗？
Can we do that?
天啊
Oh God...
你好
Hello?!
你是谁
Who are you?
没有别人在这儿 只有你我 和丽娅
There isn't anyone here It's just you and me and Leah.
我知道我看到了什么
I know what I saw.
- 是她… - 米娅
- It was her... - Mia...
发生了一些事 我…
There are things happening that I. That I...
- 我无法解释 - 什么事？
- That I can't explain. - What things?
宝贝 你…你确定不是焦虑造成的？
Baby... Are you sure they're not just manifestations of your anxiety?
新妈妈常会经历产后…
It's perfectly normal for new mothers to experience postpartum...
你是医生 不代表你什么都是专家 好吧
You know that being a doctor doesn't make you an expert on everything right?
我想我们应该找人谈谈
I think we should talk to someone.
比如？
Like who?
心理医生？
A shrink?
我没疯 约翰 我没疯
I'm not crazy John I'm not crazy
我不是说你疯了 好吗？
I'm not saying that you're crazy okay?
我说的也不是心理医生
And I'm not talking about a shrink.
所以我们就到教会来了 神父
So we turn to the church Father.
我父母就是这样 在他们…
It's what my parents did when they...
遇到难题的时候 并且对他们有用
hit a rough patch. And it worked for them.
我明白 当然
I understand of course.
但你们俩遇到的并不只是一个小难题
But you two hit more than just a rough patch.
在几个月时间里 你们经历了人生最可怕的
In a matter of months you've experienced the very worst of life...
和最美好的
And the very best.
如此巨大的变动
A pendulum swing like that.
足以撼动最坚实的基础
It's enough to shake even the strongest foundations.
但你们熬过去了
But you survived.
相反于努力忘记这次不好的记忆
And instead of trying to forget this bad history...
我想你们应该加以利用
I think you should use it
作为你们两个齐心协力是很强大的实例
as an example of how strong you two can be when united.
经历过这种事你们并没有变得更软弱
You don't come out the other side of something like this weaker.
而是更坚强
You come out stronger.
你说得对
You're right.
很好
Good.
- 米娅 是吧 - 是的
- Mia right? - Yes.
我当然记得丽娅了
And of course I remember Leah.
你是…
You are...
- 嗨 约翰 - 嗨
- Hi John. - Hi.
这位就是伊芙林 约翰 我跟你提起书店的那位女士
This is Evelyn Jones. From the bookstore I was telling you about.
对啊 是是 谢谢你送的书
All right yeah yeah... Thank you for the book.
我情不自禁啊 看到你家的姑娘们 我…
I couldn't help myself I saw your girls and I...
就觉得和她们相识已久了
I felt like I had known them a long time.
那么 一家三口要去哪儿呢
So! Where's this beautiful family off to?
- 他们是… - 我得去医院
- Oh they're just... - I have to get to the hospital.
- 今天值夜班 - 我看是他干了坏事儿
- They put me on the night shift. - I think he did something terrible.
他们说我是得到嘉奖呢
They say that I'm being rewarded.
好 如果你们想在这附近转转
Well. If you guys ever want a tour of the neighbourhood...
请尽管打给我
Don't hesitate to call me.
- 祝你们今天愉快 - 拜
- Blessed day! - Bye.
我们也该走了 早安
We should probably go too Good morning.
来人啊
Help me!
救救我
抱歉
I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 谢谢你来见我 - 没什么的
- Thank you for meeting with me. - It's fine.
不过接到你的电话我有点意外
I was a little surprised to hear from you though.
- 上次我们讲话… - 我说我不想再知道任何事
- Last time we spoke... - I said I didn't want to know any more.
保持…保持了一点距离 我…
Having... Had a little distance I...
我认识到我需要一个…一个了结
Well I realize I could use some... some closure.
我是说 有太多没有解答的问题了
I mean there... there's just to many unanswered questions.
我明白
I understand.
我带来了有关希金斯一案的资料
I brought what I have on the Higgins case.
这个是安娜贝尔 希金斯家的女儿
That's Annabelle there The Higgins girl.
照片显然是在她加入邪教之前拍的
That was clearly taken before she got caught up in the cult.
和你上次见到她是十分不同 是吧？
Looks a lot different than the last time you saw her doesn't she?
她加入的邪教
This cult that she was in.
你有进一步调查吗？
Did you look further into it?
具体查什么？
For what specifically?
我不知道 他们的袭击肯定是有动机的
I don't know There must have been some motive for their attacks.
- 疯人干疯事儿 - 疯事儿 我知道
- Crazy people do crazy things... - Crazy things I know.
他们不认为自己疯了
They didn't think they were crazy.
他们肯定是有原因的
They have to have had a reason.
在进一步调查后
After a little more digging...
我确实发现他们的行为是有信仰的
I did find that their act was in devotional.
他们是…
That they were...
他们其实是想召唤什么
They were actually trying to conjure something up.
- 什么？ - 恶魔 魔鬼
- Like... Like what? - The Devil. Demons...
牙仙什么的 具体我并不清楚
The Tooth-fairy I don't know specifically.
- 不过不重要 - 为什么？
- It doesn't really matter any. - Why not?
因为整件事就是骗人的
Well because this is all just a bunch of hocus pocus.
拜托了
Please.
女士
Ma'am.
这些人都是歹徒
These were miscreants.
谁知道他们是嗑了什么药
They were probably hopped up on god knows what.
让他们…看到…做出各种…
And it made 'em... see and do all sorts of...
可怕的事
terrible things.
这对你来说重要吗？
Does this mean anything to you?
你有听过一句话
Have you ever heard the expression...
"有时雪茄只是雪茄"？
"sometimes a cigar is just a cigar"?
那你不会介意我…留下
Then you won't mind if I keep this...
一张吧
one for myself?
还有件事 这个邪教有名字吗？
One more thing Does the cult have a name?
他们自称为"冥界使徒"
They called themselves: "The Disciples of the Realm".
又见面了
Hello again.
有什么我可以帮你的？
Is there anything I can help you with?
不不不 我只是…
Oh no no no I. I'm just...
随便看看
just browsing really.
我发现了一件事
I just learned something.
你很不会撒谎
You're a terrible liar.
你要找什么？
What is it you're looking for?
- 我还是改天再来吧 - 米娅
- Maybe I'll come back. - Mia!
我岁数大了
I'm old.
所以没多少事情能吓到我了
Which means that there's very little that surprises me anymore.
即便有 我也懒得表现出来了
And if it does I'm too tired to show it.
现在你要告诉我吗？还是我们…
Now Are you gonna tell me? Or are we just...
我觉得我们家在被一个…一个鬼魂纠缠
I think my family is being haunted by a ghost.
第四排 跟我来
AIsle four Follow me.
我知道听上去很扯
I...I know it sounds crazy.
这个女孩的鬼魂缠着我们 但是我…我…
The ghost of this girl haunting us. But I... I just...
没有比分开红海更扯的了
No crazier than the red sea parting.
对没信仰的人来说 全都很扯
To non-believers it's all crazy.
你相信这种东西吗？
Do you believe in this stuff?
只能说
Let's just say that...
我这辈子有过一两次经历
I've had one or two experiences in my life that eh...
让我什么都能接受
helped me to keep an open mind.
我并不认为你所碰到的 是那个女孩的鬼魂
I don't particularly think what you are experiencing is the ghost of that girl.
为什么？
Why not?
鬼会徘徊在一些特别的地方
Well ghosts haunts specific places.
通常都发生过可怕的事情
Usually where something terrible has happened.
比如你们过去的房子
Like your old house.
我们…搬家了 可还是会发生
We... We moved and it's still happening.
所以我才不认为是鬼
Which is why I don't think it's a ghost.
但是那个邪教
But now that cult...
你说他们是想召唤什么？
You said that they were trying to summon something?
根据我曾看到过的
From what I've read in the past...
这些邪教不是召唤鬼魂
These cults they don't summon ghosts.
而是召唤人的灵魂
They summon in human spirits.
肉身里从不曾存在的东西
Something that has never existed in the flesh.
恶魔？
Demons?
他们想要怎样呢？
What... What do they want?
一个灵魂
A soul.
并且不达目的不罢休
And they won't stop until they get one.
我该 我该怎么办？
What do I... What do I do?
希望这些书中能找到答案
Hopefully the answer is in one of these books.
我女儿 露比
My daughter Ruby.
她在你这个岁数去世了
She passed away when she was about your age.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
失去她 我觉得生无可恋
Without her I felt like I had nothing else to live for so...
但就在我等着一切结束的时候
But as I lay there waiting for it all to end...
我听到她的声音
I heard her voice.
告诉我 我的时候未到
She told me that it wasn't my time.
上帝对我另有安排
That God had another purpose for me.
你也有你的安排 米娅
You too have a purpose Mia.
保护家人
To protect your family.
所以不要认为自己这样做是发疯
So don't think you're crazy for trying to do that.
你是做你认为对的事
You do what you think is right.
做你必须做的事
You do what you have to do.
魔鬼专门折磨软弱和脆弱之人
The Devil preys on the weak and the vulnerable.
企图吞噬他们的灵魂
Seeking to devour their souls.
施展…魔咒
To perform... Incantations...
洒下近亲之血
Spilling the blood of kin.
洒下纯洁之血
Spilling the blood of the innocent.
我该如何阻止？
How do I stop it?
丽娅
Leah!
出什么事了
What happened?
什么事？你得想想办法
Happened? You gotta help this travesty.
- 谢谢你前来 神父 - 没什么的
- Thank you for coming Father. - Yes. Of course.
米娅
Mia.
这个娃娃 我能看看吗？
This Doll May I see it?
- 约翰丢掉过 - 或者说曾经试图
- John got rid of her. - Or tried to.
可她却出现在我们某个箱子的最下面
There she was at the bottom of one of our last boxes.
我还是不明白娃娃跟这个所谓的魔鬼有什么关系
I still don't understand what the doll has to with this supposed demon.
恶魔有时可以利用物体作为
Demons can sometimes use objects as conduits
达到其需求目标的渠道
to achieve their desired goal.
需求目标？
Their desired goal?
我们的灵魂 约翰
Our souls John.
所以它会来找丽娅
That's why it's after Leah.
- 它想要她的灵魂 - 不 不 不
- It wants her soul. - No no no.
恶魔不能随便夺走人的灵魂 米娅
Demons can't just take souls Mia.
灵魂需要先献给魔鬼 才可能被其带走
The soul needs to be offered to the demon before it can take it.
我暂时还不打算把显出我的灵魂
Well I don't plan on offering my soul anytime soon.
魔鬼就是撒旦
The Devil is the father of lies.
恶魔是他的操控者
Demons are his manipulators.
没有人会想献出自己的灵魂
No one ever plans to offer their soul.
我们该怎么摆脱？
How can we get rid of it?
该如何阻止它再来？
How do we stop it from coming back?
目前我还不知道
I don't know Not yet.
但教会有人或许懂
But someone at the church might.
起码我听说有一对夫妻
At the very least I've heard of a married couple
过去曾经和教会合作过
that the church has worked with in the past
专门处理这种事情
that deal with this kind of thing.
他们在东部 不过总可以打个电话的
They're back east but a call can always be placed.
在此期间 我们怎么做？
What do we do in the meantime?
我不能让丽娅再接近那个娃娃
I can't have Leah anywhere near that doll.
把她交给我
Let me take her.
或许把她放在神圣的地方 会减弱恶魔的力量
Perhaps if she's stored in a sacred place it will weaken the demon enough.
让它没办法再回来
It won't have the strength to return.
- 谢谢你 神父 - 没什么
- Thank you Father. - Of course.
来吧 你要上床睡觉 这是医嘱
Come on Let's get you to bed Doctors orders.
不 不 约翰 我睡不着 除非我知道它不会再来
Oh no no John I can't Not until I know it's not coming back.
- 米娅 - 好了 那这样 这样…
- Mia. - Come on What if. what if...
- 约翰 我做不到 - 我来守着她怎么样？
- John I can't. - What if I just stayed up with her?
你去休息
You get some rest.
- 好吗？ - 好
- Alright? - Okay.
晚安
Good night.
约翰
John.
嗯
Yeah.
谢谢你相信我
Thank you for believing me.
我不知道你会不会信我…
I didn't know if... if you would.
米娅
Mia!
好了 我爱你
Come on I love you.
我永远都会相信你的
I will always believe you.
晚安
Good night.
你觉得佩雷斯神父会帮我们吗？
Do you think Father Perez is gonna help us?
他会的 我相信
Yeah I do.
不是吧
Come on.
愿上帝垂怜你
May God have mercy on your soul!!
说实话 米娅
Frankly Mia...
这与你无关
It's none of your business.
是我和丽娅
This is between me and Leah.
她说她想要那套睡衣
And she said she wanted those pajamas.
你会宠坏她的
You're gonna spoil her.
我没机会当外婆
I didn't have a chance for grandkids.
再说孩子怎么充都不为过
Besides it's impossible to spoil a baby.
这我可不知道
I don't know if that's the truth.
对丽娅 我们就要这么想 因为…
We just have to take that up with Leah because
她还指了这些裙子
she also pointed out these dresses.
伊芙林
Oh Evelyn.
亲爱的
Oh sweetie-pie.
哭得越来越凶 哎哟哟
Oh it get's crazier Oh mommy.
好了 听我说
Okay. You know what?
我的露比以前也总是闹 直到我摇晃她
My Ruby used to fuzz and fuzz until I rocked her.
把她放下
Put her down here.
她以前就总是哭闹 来
She used to fuzz and fuzz Come on.
过来 丽娅
Come here Leah.
好了 丽娅 好 就是这样
All right Leah Okay Here we go.
这就对了丽娅
Here we go Leah.
我们摇晃着宝宝一整晚
We gonna rock that baby all night long
你真是我的大救星
You are a lifesaver.
你刚哼唱的什么？
What was it that you were humming?
一个布鲁斯小调
Oh. A little blues ditty.
我的露比小时候 只有听到这个才会安静下来
It was the only thing that would settle my Ruby down when she was a baby
介意我问下她是怎么去世的吗？
Do you mind if I ask how she passed?
你要是不想说 完全没问题的
I don't mind if. If you don't wanna talk about it...
不会 没什么的
Oh no It's okay.
是因为一场车祸
It was a car accident.
我们开车从我父母家回去
We were driving back from my parents.
他们住在北边 所以…
They live up north. So eh...
我当时很累 知道吗？
I was tired. You know?
家人就是很累人
Family'll do that to you.
天很晚了 我不该开车的
It was very late and I shouldn't have been behind the wheel.
我只记得
Last thing I remember was...
我当时看向副驾驶
Looking over in the passengers seat.
我的女儿睡着了
At my daughter Asleep.
是啊 她长成了最漂亮的小姑娘
Yeah She had grown into the most beautiful young woman.
三周后我醒来了
I woke up three weeks later.
可露比再也没有
And Ruby never did.
我都没有机会和她告别
I didn't get a chance to say goodbye.
我没有求上帝先带我走
I didn't get to beg god to take me first.
我犯了错 可是…
I made the mistake and...
却让她付出了代价
She paid the price.
神父
Father.
在哪儿？
Where is it?
- 什么？ - 那个娃娃
- Where's what? - The doll...
你拿走了啊
You took it with you.
恶魔
The Evil...
出现了
It's presence.
我看到了 约翰
I saw it John.
我感觉到了
I felt it.
感觉到了它有多想
I felt how much it wants...
想怎样
Want's what?
- 带走她的灵魂 - 可你说
- To take her soul. - But you said...
它是不能带走丽娅的 你…你说要献给它才可以
That it can't take Leah's You. You said that it has to be offered.
宝宝是不能献出自己灵魂的
A baby cannot offer its soul.
天啊
Oh my god.
米娅
Mia!
我去看孩子
Here I'll get that.
- 你好 - 米娅
- Hello? - Mia.
佩雷斯神父出了车祸 他说…
Father Perez was in an accident He said...
- 约翰？ - 米娅 米娅
- John?! - Mia Mia!
我要你马上离开房子
I need you to get out of the house.
好吗？我…
Okay? I Ne...
我现在就走
I'm leaving now.
佩雷斯神父？
Father Perez?
没出什么事吧？
Is everything all right?
神父
Father.
愿上帝垂怜你
MAY GOD HAVE MERCY ON YOUR SOUL!
是谁啊
Who is that?
我们得离开这里
We need to leave.
丽娅
Leah!
丽娅 丽娅
Leah Leah!
米娅 电话坏了 快来
Mia The phone is dead. Come on.
- 等等 等下 - 我们得去我那儿
- Wait wait wait! - We'll have to go to my apartment.
你得跟我来
You need to come with me,
不 我要去找丽娅
No I need to find Leah.
我们会找她的 得先去教堂 他们会帮我们的
We'll get her back. We need to get the church. They'll help us.
快来
Come!
丽娅
Leah!
你想从我这儿得到什么？
What do you want from me?
你想要什么？
把她还给我
Give her back to me.
你还给我
You give her back.
丽娅
Leah!
丽娅 我的宝贝
Leah my baby!
上帝啊 不要
Oh please God no!
拜托 她在哪儿？
Oh Please! Where is she?!
肯定有别的办法的
There has to be another way.
你的灵魂
Your soul...
妈妈会救你的 丽娅 妈妈会…
Mommy's gonna save you Leah Mommy's gonna...
米娅
Mia!
妈妈来了
Mommy's coming...
米娅
Mia!
- 她在里面 我进不去 - 米娅 米娅
- She's in there I can't get in. - Mia! MIA!
米娅 不 不不
Mia! No no no no no.
站住
Stop.
别过来
好了好了 听我说
Okay okay okay Hear Listen to me.
请你下来
Please Come down.
- 它带走了我的孩子 - 拜托 你得下来
- It took my baby. - Please You gotta come down.
拜托你下来 好吗
Please come down Okay?
它要她的灵魂 我要把我的给它 约翰
It wants her soul I have to give it mine John.
米娅 不要
Mia! No!
不要那么做
Don't do it.
- 它不会把她还给我的 除非… - 不 不要
- It won't give her back unless I... - No! No!
米娅 听我说
Mia! Listen to me.
丽娅需要你 好吗 亲爱的 我需要你
Leah needs you here Okay sweetie? I need you here.
请不要这样做
Please don't do this.
我爱你 约翰
I love you John.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道你会照顾好我们的丽娅
I know you'll take good care of our Leah.
你每晚都会亲吻她
You kiss her every night.
等她长大了 约翰 告诉她我很爱她
When she's old enough John you tell her that I loved her.
不
No!
约翰 不
John! No!
停下 好了
Stop Stop.
- 约翰 它要她的灵魂 - 米娅 不要
- John It wants her soul. - Mia Stop Stop.
我的宝贝
My baby!
米娅 听他的话 你不能这么对丽娅
Mia Listen to him You can't do this to Leah.
- 女儿需要她的妈妈 - 你说它需要一个灵魂
- A daughter needs her mother. - You said it needs a soul.
你说过它需要一个灵魂
You said it needs a soul!
- 别这样 - 请让我救她
- Please... - Please let me save her.
你不会想这么做的
You don't wanna do this
- 好了 冷静 停下 - 不
- Stop stop stop! - No!
你说过你会救她的 你说过你会先救她
You said you'd save her. You said you'd save her before me.
- 你答应过的 - 想想我们的孩子 想想丽娅
- You promised... - Think about our baby. Think about Leah.
好吗？想想她 拜托
Okay? Think about her Please.
- 不要这么对我们 - 它要她的灵魂
- Don't do this to us! - It wants her soul.
- 肯定有别的办法的 - 有的
- There has to be another way. - There is.
我可以挽回一切
I can make it right.
这是露比的意思
This is what Ruby meant.
不不
Oh No no.
上帝重视牺牲
God honors sacrifice.
我们的牺牲会打动上帝的心
And our sacrifices touch Gods heart.
感动他的手
And move his hand.
耶稣说 这是我的命令
Jesus said: This is my commandment.
要像我爱你般爱彼此
That you love one another as I have loved you.
没有比这更伟大的爱
Greater love hath no-one but this:
为朋友舍命
That he lay down his life for his friends.
我们来祷告吧
Let us pray.
(六个月后)
很精彩的布道
Wonderful sermon.
- 你精神不错 神父 - 谢谢 米娅
- You look well father! - Thank you Mia.
你们好吗？
And how are you doing?
我们现在好多了 谢谢
We're doing much better now. Thank you.
那个娃娃有消息吗？
Has there been any sign of the doll?
没 从那晚后就没有 我想是警察拿走了
No Not since that night I thought the police took it.
不过克拉金警探那边没有记录
But Detective Clarkin has no record of it.
但邪恶时常发生
But evil is constant.
你无法毁灭根本不存在的东西
You cannot destroy what was never created.
我只希望不管是谁遇到了那个娃娃
I just pray that whomever comes into contact with the doll next
都会得到他们需要的帮助
gets the help they need.
我们也是
So do we.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
- 拜 神父 - 拜 米娅
- Bye Father. - Bye Mia.
我差点忘了
I almost forgot.
真漂亮 谢谢你 神父
Oh It's beautiful. Thank you father.
上帝心中最美丽的杰作
The loveliest masterpiece at the heart of God...
就是一个母亲的爱
Is the love of a mother.
谢谢
Thank you.
有什么我可以帮你的？
Anything I can help you with?
我只是想找样东西送我女儿
I'm just trying to find something for my daughter.
谢谢
Thanks.
她是护士 总是帮助他人
She's a nurse. Always helping people.
我们到处找 就想找这个
We looked everywhere for one of these.
从来没有找到过
Never did find one.
应该是个收藏品
It's a collectors item supposedly.
所以我们价格定得略高
That's why we prize it a little higher than the rest.
- 要我包起来吗？ - 是的 谢谢
- You want me to ring it up? - Yes please.
安娜贝尔如今被装进了一个玻璃盒
放置在艾德和洛林·华伦的艺术品收藏室内
每个月会请牧师来净化两次
邪恶的威胁向来存在…
只要我们提高警惕,便可加以控制，但永远无法真正将其消灭